It is one of our problems.
But the risk of an ordinary citizen, should you be afraid when you come here?
I don't think you should be afraid but there is an increased risk I would say.
It is not completely problem -free, especially in the evening as ordinary people are not so much out.
But what are these problems because do you think it will be gang crime and some become criminals?
It is some kind of exclusion, you feel no hope and do not believe in your ability to succeed.
You do not have the right role models.
You see that some sell and make money and think that is the way to go.
It is very easy to end up there.
That's one of the problems.
Is it young ages too or?
Above all, many people at a young age are 10-12 years old until you are around 20 years old.
Most leave the crime.
What do you think you should do more?
I guess the police need more resources and such, what do you think?
We need to work in two places I usually say.
We need to work with the social stuff, trying to make people feel involved in society, try-
-He more role models, be present, create a good relationship and make people feel hope for the future.
But then we also need to sharpen and screw to certain legislation.
If you commit crimes, if you throw stones at police or threaten someone, there should be consequences.
It should not take that long.
If you are suspected of crime, it should not take a year before you are sentenced.
If you are convicted of a crime over and over again, it should not be enough to get a conditional sentence.
It must be screwed up so we can signal to everyone else that if you do not take care of it, there will be consequences.
You said earlier that is what many want here?